My name is Ivy.
我叫常春藤。
I study at the Duke University for the MEng program,
我在杜克大学攻读工学硕士课程，
aka Master of Engineering program,
又名工程硕士课程，
and I'm studying Electrical and Computer Engineering.
我正在学习电气和计算机工程。
Is a really awesome experience to be
作为这所
a student in this university and in this program,
大学和这个课程的学生是一次非常棒的经历
and I learn a lot here.
，我在这里学到了很多东西。
For some new programmer,
对于一些新手程序员来说，
people may think that programming is
人们可能会认为编程
totally magic but actually is not.
完全是神奇的，但实际上不是。
Everything is following the logic
一切都遵循逻辑
and have to make sense in the programming world.
，在编程世界中必须有意义。
So first, you need to trust
因此，首先，你需要相信
the logic rather than just think random things.
逻辑，而不仅仅是随机思考。
Then also for the programming,
那么对于编程来说，
planning is something that you
计划也是你
have to really take into consideration.
必须真正考虑的事情。
So rather than just put some random things and
因此，
you actually need to first make plans,
实际上，与其随机放一些东西，假装自己在屏幕前工作，然后在键盘上打字，不如先制定计划，
draw pictures, and seriously
画画，然后认真
think about what you need to do.
思考需要做什么。
Then puts things implemented
然后将
actually in the programming world.
实际实现的东西放在编程世界中。
Also, in Duke University especially,
此外，尤其是在杜克大学，
the professor and all their courses is
教授及其所有课程都经过
very well planned and designed.
精心策划和设计。
So trust all the course project
因此，
you have to do and do it step-by-step,
请相信你必须完成的所有课程项目并逐步完成，
you'll finally be a awesome programmer.
你最终将成为一名出色的程序员。
There's tons of project I've
在
finished in the whole program.
整个项目中，我已经完成了很多项目。
One thing I really wanted to talk about is
我真正想谈的一件事是
the UPS and Amazon project.
UPS 和亚马逊项目。
I've done in the server-less software class.
我已经在无服务器软件课上完成了。
So basically what's happening is that
因此，基本上正在发生的事情是，
one team need to in-charge of the UPS system,
一个团队需要负责UPS系统
and another team need to be in
，另一个团队需要
charge of the Amazon system.
负责亚马逊系统。
We need to design the protocol
我们需要
altogether to make everything work.
完全设计协议才能让一切顺利进行。
This project is very special for me because it
这个项目对我来说非常特别，因为它
actually mimics what is happening in the industry life.
实际上模仿了行业生活中正在发生的事情。
Because in industry there's no way you can
因为在工业中，你不可能
finish your whole system by yourself or even by one team.
自己甚至一个团队完成整个系统。
So what is very
因此，非常
important is that you need to learn how to
重要的是，你需要学习如何
communicate with other team and
与其他团队沟通，并
design their protocol altogether.
完全设计他们的协议。
So during the whole developing process,
因此，在整个开发过程中，
we actually need to change our protocol step-by-step,
我们实际上需要逐步更改我们的协议
and finally, get to the perfect one.
，最后，达到完美的协议。
The process is a little bit of painful,
这个过程有点痛苦，
but finally we'll put everything together and
但最后我们会把所有东西放在一起，
find the whole system work perfectly.
发现整个系统都能完美运行。
It's really good and inside peaceful and happiness.
真的很不错，里面平静而幸福。
For those students who are
对于那些
struggling in finding a job or an interview,
在找工作或面试方面苦苦挣扎的学生，
I totally understand what you're feeling right now.
我完全理解你现在的感受。
I know it is hard,
我知道这很难，
but trust me you'll be flying.
但请相信我，你会飞的。
I think for the most important things about finding
我认为，找
a job is not about how can I pass this interview,
工作最重要的事情不在于如何通过这次面试，
but how can I be a great software engineer.
而是如何才能成为一名优秀的软件工程师。
To achieve that goal all you need is to practice,
为了实现这个目标，你所需要的只是
practice, and practice following all the cross project,
按照所有跨项目以及
those professors because they have their experience,
所有这些教授的所有建议进行实践、练习和练习，因为他们有自己的经验，
and they know what the industry world need.
他们知道行业世界需要什么。
Once you get more and more comfortable
一旦你越来越
to work as a software engineer,
愿意担任软件工程师，这
the job will just come in to you.
份工作就会浮出水面。